OLABISI ADESIMBO ODUSANYA

KIELOTIE 4-6 B 82, 01300, Vantaa, Finland. |+358417406216| odus.bisi87@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Graduated from the Middlesex University with a degree in Business Information Systems and recently in Business Management from Centria University of Applied Sciences. My previous work experiences have aided me in the development of a valuable and transferrable skill set in a working environment. After working in sales for some years, I am willing to take on new and challenging tasks to aid in the gaining of new knowledge and make a positive contribution in the organisation.

Education

JANUARY 2020-MAY 2021 BUSINESS COLLEGE HELSINKI

Full-Stack Web Development Certificate

AUGUST 2017-MAY 2020 CENTRIA UNIVERSITY OF APPLIED SCIENCES, FINLAND

BSc Business Management

SEPTEMBER 2016-MAY 2017 MIDDLESEX UNIVERSITY, MALTA

BSc Business Information Systems: First Class Honours

Modules included: Strategic management and Information systems, Social, ethical and legal issues in Computing and Data Warehousing.

JANUARY 2010-DECEMBER 2012 APTECH COMPUTER EDUCATION

Advanced Diploma in Software Engineering

1997-2003 LAGOS STATE MODEL COLLEGE, KANKON, BADAGRY

Eight GSCE's at grace C and above, including Mathematics and English.

Project

• Extended project (part of degree): Web Application for Online Grocery Shopping.

Technical Skills

- Microsoft office programs
- Software packages: JavaScript, CSS, HTML5.
- MySQL
- SAP ERP S4/HANA
- Basic knowledge of python programming

Experience

BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT MANAGER | TAIWO ADEWOLE AND ASSOCIATES | NOV 2012-AUG 2016

- · Negotiating and closing business deals with clients.
- · Maintaining a good relationship with new and existing contacts.
- · Pitching goods and services to customers and updating them of any changes.
- · Analyzing market strategies before closing a deal.

FRONT DESK OFFICER | ADNAT TELECOMMUNICATIONS AND ELECTRONICS LIMITED | MARCH 2006-NOV 2010

- · Meeting and welcoming customers.
- · Ordering of office supplies, preparing and arranging meeting hall.
- · Organizing travel plans and keeping the senior managers updated on appointments.

SALES ASSISTANT | BAO TEXTILES LIMITED | APRIL 2004-FEB 2006

- . Welcoming customers and responding to inquiries
- . Displaying sales items in an attractive manner
- . Providing customer service

Hobbies

• Enjoy travelling, long walks, cooking, singing, dancing and reading.